Hey founders, I'm Pratyush, neuro-hacker someone who systematically measures
and optimizes brain function. Right now,
I'm streaming my own EEG data live showing the technical,
electrical patterns of my brain as I speak.
Over the past one year, I've logged more than 1000 hours of data from
EEG headsets, heart rate,
variability, sensors, whoop wearable,
mood and focus applications like Animi and sleep trackers and
journaling, I've tested 50 plus nootropics,
dozens of meditation techniques, acupuncture sessions,
and talktherapy. My conclusion,
all these tools work, but facing together what actually moves the needle takes
hundreds of tedious hours. Time that something most people simply don't have.
So I'm building some building a platform that works as both
a universal tracker and an experimentation engine.
So in this engine, first the user integrates everything their variable data,
their self-reported surveys and mood logs,
habit tracking and journal entries, once all that data is collected,
the AI model identifies the user's limitations.
For example, one cannot focus for more than 30 hours,
30 minutes. And as the AI identifies
the limitations for the users, they also build and design
these personalized protocol suggestions,
which is based on the user's data,
the neuroscience research, as well as community tested routines.
Once the user has this protocol,
they can test the protocol track-the-outcome and share the results back with the community.
And I was inspired by Elizabeth Ricker's Smarter tomorrow
which shows that just 15 minutes of targeted brain training-per-day body
can transform performance. My platform automates the four steps
that are highlighted in the book, tracking,
identifying, experimenting, and measuring.
So any user does not have to spend one piecing it all together and
who benefits from this platform. engineers who're trying to extend their deep focus
sessions, founders managing real-time fundraising stress,
artists breaking through creative jobs, and people struggling with
mental illness trying to get out of their struggles,
all through personalized data-driven neuro-hacking,
amplified by a global community of contributors,
sharing what works for them. At off season I want to democratize
brain optimization, making peak cognitive performance accessible to
everyone with down to $1,000 hours worth.
That's just me, the neuro-hacker.